从上一集的《终空》里我们得知
Previously on "Final Space"...
最后的最后  盖瑞和阿瓦卡多
At long last, Gary and Avocato
终于把阿瓦卡多的儿子  小卡多
rescue Avocato's son, Little Cato,
从总司令的魔爪里救了出来
from the clutches of the Lord Commander,
但那个魔头也展开了复仇
but that dick weed takes revenge
他扔出一枚炸弹  而阿瓦卡多及时发现了它
and teleports a bomb that Avocato finds just in time
也因此牺牲了性命  只为拯救他的爱子
to sacrifice his life to save his son.
我知道  我也很怀念他
I know. I'll miss him, too.
你还有3分钟氧气可用
You have three minutes of oxygen left.
好冷啊  HUE  你冷吗？
It's cold, H.U.E. Are you cold?
我只能感受到两样东西  盖瑞  那就是无物和无为
I only feel two things, Gary... nothing and nothingness.
你知道吗？
You know what?
是因为那些阴影
It's the shade.
阴影里总是冷上个十来度
It's always, like, 10 degrees colder... in the shade.
宇宙完全是由阴影构成的
Space is made entirely of shade.
是啊  我猜如此
Yeah, I guess it is.
我要找点“非阴影”
I gotta find some of that non-shade.
然而到底他妈在哪啊？
Where the hell is it?
哦  嘿  哦
Oh, hey. Oh.
哦  嘣  非阴影
Oh, boom ... non-shade.
狗带！现在又他喵的热到爆炸了
Crap! It's, like, really freakin' piping hot now.
鸭嘴兽字幕组出品
翻译 + 专访听译 + 校对 + 压制：Kyl
Final Space - Chapter Seven
终空  第一季第七集
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com
本字幕仅供学习交流  请于下载后24小时内删除
阿瓦卡多？
Avocato?
你离开已经是三天前的事了
It's been three days since you died.
我得承认... 我现在备受煎熬
I have to say I'm... I'm struggling here, man.
你叫我照顾好你的儿子
You said to look after your boy,
但我现在连自己都照顾不好
and I can barely look after myself.
我真的觉得你找错人了
I really think you picked the wrong guy.
当然了  你能选的人也不多  但是
Granted, there wasn't a big pool to pick from, but...
我想说的是
I guess what I'm trying to say is...
我好想你  伙计
I miss you, friend.
你觉得我该做什么？
What do you think I should do?
我  我需要点提示啊  老天
I mean, I-I... I need a sign, man.
你可以  敲敲玻璃杯什么的
You know, maybe rattle some glasses
让我多给他点自由空间  或者让灯闪几下
if I should give him some space or flicker the lights.
哪怕闪一下也好  那我就对他多用点心
You know, just a little flicker if I should try harder.
无论怎么装神弄鬼发出点提示都好
Any ghost-related stuff at all would be great.
或者就什么都不做  这样也成吧
Or nothing. Nothing works, too.
图雷斯
60103区
- 你小子在干什么？！   - KVN 在帮忙修东西
- What the crap are you doing?! - KVN is making helpful repairs.
看啊！焕然一新！这样就没洞了
There! Boomtown! No more hole.
洞？！那是厕所大门啊！
Hole?! That was the door to the bathroom!
噢！我还以为那是个长方形的大洞呢
Oh! I thought it was a huge rectangular hole.
- 啊！   - 毛线！那个长方形大洞是厕所门啊！
- Ugh! - How?! That huge rectangular hole was the door to the bathroom!
- 你确定？   - 我确定！确定  我  我确定！
- You sure? - Yes! Yes, I'm ... Yes!
好吧  你倒来气了
Well, that puts you in a situation, huh?
盖瑞？
Gary?
嗯？
Yeah?
我有个消息要告诉你
I have news for you.
什么消息  HUE？
What is it, H.U.E.?
三  二  一
Three, two, one...
盖瑞  你在银河一号上的刑期结束了
Gary, your prison sentence aboard the Galaxy 1 is now complete.
好极... 等等  你说什么？
That's gre... Wait, say what?
你自由了  盖瑞
You're free, Gary.
自由？不是开玩笑的？
Free? This isn't a joke?
我  我真的自由了？
I mean, I-I'm really free?
是的  盖瑞  你现在打算做什么？
Yes, Gary. What are you going to do now?
太棒了！哦  我自由了！
Yes! Oh, I'm free!
过了这么多年  那些饼干终于归我了！
All these long years, and these freedom cookies are mine!
盖瑞  你应该和小卡多聊聊
Gary? You should talk to Little Cato.
“我觉得你需要和小卡多聊聊”
"I think you need to talk to Little Cato.
“我觉得你需要  呃  爬进通风管道里和小卡多聊聊”
I think you need to, uh, crawl in a vent and talk to Little Cato."
嘿  你这些饼干都是哪来的？
Hey, where'd you get all those cookies?
- 你想吃吗？它们烂极了   - 是的  它们确实烂极了
- You want them? They suck. - They do. They do suck!
等了五年  等来这些小圆垃圾
Five years for these little round pieces of suckage!
快说正事  我很忙的
Get to the point. I'm a busy guy.
呃  嗯
Well, hmm.
好吧  小家伙  我怎么能让你开心起来？
All right, buddy, what can I do to make you happy?
- 你列出什么都成   - 什么都成？
- Name anything. - Anything?
- 什么他妈都成   - 什么都成？
- Freakin' anything. - Anything?
我说了  什么他妈都成
I just said freakin' anything. Anything.
你能带我去见总司令吗？
Can you get me to the Lord Commander?
好吧  我似乎可以做到  你想干什么？
Okay... possibly. What do you want to do?
我想把他的喉咙割开
I want to slit his throat
让他鲜血四溅
and splash in his life juice.
哦  我的天哪  太阴暗了  呃
Oh. Good Lord, that's dark. Okay, well...
听起来是个不错的主意
Sounds like a fantastic idea.
算我一个！
Count me in!
我从来没有想过
I never thought I'd be creating
能和一个小男孩组成谋杀小队  不过我们做到了
a murder squad with a small boy, but here we are.
这是  这是我爸的房间吗？
Is this... Is this my father's room?
是的  正是
Hell yeah, it is.
哦  我的天哪  看起来乱极了
Oh, my gosh, look at all the crap.
好吧  我记得阿瓦卡多有个大扫帚来着
All right, well, Avocato's gotta have big boom sticks in here somewhere.
- 你觉得他怎么样？   - 你爸？
- What did you think of him? - Your dad?
嗯  他是一个急性子  怒气冲冲  爱发脾气
Well, he was a short-tempered, angry grouch.
但我就喜欢他这样
I loved that about him.
我也是  另外他真的很关心你
Me, too. Plus, he cared about you.
天啊  他关心你胜过一切
Man, I mean, more than anything.
- 你真这么想？   - 他一说起你就停不下来了
- You think so? - He would never shut up about you.
每天都是如此  “小卡多...”
I mean, every day, "Little Cato ...
“我们必须去救小卡多  他受伤了”
we gotta save Little Cato. He's injured.
“他是我的儿子  我们要找到他”
He's my boy. Let's find him."
我没开玩笑  他真的很爱你
You know, I do not jest, the man loved you.
他从没和告诉过我这个
He never said that to me.
他牺牲了自己的性命去救你  他用行动告诉你了
He said it when he gave his life to save you.
那是爱的行动... 以阿瓦卡多的方式
That was love in action mode... Avocato style.
我的七舅姥爷啊！成功了！
Heck chicklets! We got it!
给你！准备好了吗？
Here you go! You ready?
咱们去给总司令开个新屁眼！
Let's tear the Lord Commander a new butthole.
好的！开三个！
Yes! Maybe even three!
或者四个？四个怎么样？
Or four. Four of them?
十个吧  十个剧痛的大张的屁眼！
10. 10 painfully wide-open buttholes!
- 咱们把他打成屁眼筛子吧   - 那就是
- We're gonna cover him in buttholes. - That's a ...
那就得有50个  甚至到55个了！
that's, like, 50 to 55 buttholes right there!
KVN也想把他打成屁眼筛子！
KVN wants to cover him in buttholes, too!
我们也要来  看他怎么办！
We're coming, deal with it!
好的  那我们就叫“把烂脾气的
All right, fine. We shall be called the Legion of Murdering
暴力薰心的矮子恶魔
an Irritatingly Power-thirsty Pint-sized Imp
打成屁眼筛子军团”吧！
into a Plethora of Butthoooooles!
奎恩  还有48小时  缺口就要把地球吞噬了
Quinn, only 48 hours till the breach consumes Earth.
在飞船修好之前
Until we fix the ship,
我们不能启动光折引擎
we cannot engage our lightfold engines,
而且你眼下有个更紧急的问题
and you have a more immediate problem.
HUE  他在干什么？
H.U.E., what is he doing?
我只能猜测一下
I can only hypothesize,
不过我感觉他们要去干一架
but I think they are going to pick a fight.
那个白痴！
That idiot!
盖瑞  我们没空做这个！
Gary, we don't have time for this!
我们有更麻烦的问题！
We've got bigger problems!
哦没错  还没音乐呢！谢了  奎恩
Oh, right. Tunes! Thanks, Quinn.
HUE  放点好听的
H.U.E., play the good stuff.
来点冲锋号  或者雨声器
I'm talking about war trumpets, rain sticks,
雨声器（rain stick）：一种简单的敲击乐器，是传统部落用来祭天求雨的法器。
或者让人灵魂为之一振的双簧弯管
soul-crushing crumhorns
让这些愉快的伙计们心潮起伏吧
to stir the hearts of these merry men.
- 再来点短笛和单簧管   - 不许放短笛和单簧管！
- And piccolos and clarinets. - No piccolos or clarinets!
- 那就天籁小提琴   - 不行！
- Right. Angelic violins. - No!
哦  HUE  这是什么鬼！
Oh, H.U.E., what is this?
你不是要放点好听的吗  盖瑞
The good stuff, Gary.
这一点也不好听！
That is not the good stuff!
冲锋号呢  雨声器呢？
Where are the war trumpets, the rain sticks?
这太令人伤心了  盖瑞
This is so sad, Gary.
它让我想起了那些我曾经爱过的人
It makes me think about all the people I've loved
- 我爱过的人  已经不在人世了   - 别  别说了
- who have died, like ... - Don't ... Don't say it.
- 阿瓦卡多   - 哦！
- Avocato. - Oh!
我兄弟已经死了！
My bro is dead!
- 你能上那边哭去吗？   - 也许我确实该过去
- Can you take all of that over there? - Maybe I should.
对不起  我没事  我没想到我的情感屏障
Sorry, small fry. I didn't foresee my emotional shielding
如此不堪一击！
getting shut down so quickly!
Chookity!
闭嘴  月饼！
Shut the hell up, Mooncake!
哦老天  我好难过！
Oh, I'm so sad!
小卡多  根据我的监测  总司令
Little Cato, I am not detecting the Lord Commander
不在这个大火炉里
on that heavy incinerator.
我不管  这是在给我爸复仇！
I don't care. This is for my dad!
事后回想起来  这并非一个好主意
In hindsight, this wasn't the greatest idea.
那是啥？！
What was that?!
盖瑞  你还好吗？盖瑞？盖瑞？！
Gary, are you okay? Gary? Gary?!
盖瑞！
Gary!
哦  我的声音处理模块  我听不见你了
Oh, my audio processing unit. I can't hear you.
什么  什么？什么  什么？
What, what? What, what?
你还好吗？喂  醒醒
Small fry? Hey, wake up.
你刚说话了吗？
Did you say something?
阿瓦卡多选了最差劲的人来保护他的儿子
Avocato picked the worst guy to watch over his son.
我简直是吸引厄运的磁石
I am a bad-luck magnet.
他还有呼吸吗？
Is he breathing?
好消息是  小卡多还有呼吸
Great news, guys. Little Cato is breathing.
你救了我
You saved my life.
- 你是谁？   - 你好啊  盖瑞
- Who are you? - Hi, Gary.
- 奎恩？！   - 盖瑞  我...
- Quinn?!  - Gary, I...
这他喵的是啥？
What the tough titty wompas?
你是谁？
Who are you?
- 啥？   - 我是你
- Wha? - I'm you.
可你不能是我
But you can't be me.
我这么说是因为  我已经是我了
I know that because I'm already me.
- 啥？   - 不  我真的是你
- What? - No, I'm really you,
- 只不过是来自未来的你   - 嗨  未来的奎恩  我是KVN
- just from the future. - Hey, future Quinn, I'm KVN,
盖瑞的深空防精神错乱伴侣
Gary's deep-space insanity avoidance companion.
我们是最最要好的朋友
We're just the bestest of friends.
- 住嘴  KVN   - 老天啊  好性感
- Shut up, KVN. - Good Lord, that's hot.
但现在两个我同时出现了  难道不矛盾吗？
But the two of us together, isn't that a paradox?
- 宇宙难道不会爆炸吗？   - 这是个很好的问题
- Shouldn't the universe explode? - Excellent question.
- 显然不会   - 这是个很好的答案
- Apparently not. - Excellent answer.
- 但  为什么？   - 因为爱因斯坦是个混蛋
- But... why? - 'Cause Einstein's a jerk.
我怎么会知道？
How am I supposed to know?
如果这对你来说容易一些的话  你可以叫我我的代号
If it helps, you can call me by my code name ...
- 我叫夜幕   - 夜幕？听上去蠢爆了
- Nightfall. - Nightfall? That's super lame.
- 是我起的名字吗？   - 不  是他起的
- Did I come up with that? - No. He did.
奎恩  奎恩  别和自己打架了
Quinns, Quinns, stop fighting with yourselves.
不得不说  盖瑞  我想念你的智慧
Gotta say, Gary, I missed your wit.
智慧？！他才把小卡多带到一个自杀任务里！
Wit?! He took Little Cato on a stupid suicide mission!
你到底行不行啊？！你让我们大家都身处险境
What's wrong with you?! You're a danger to all of us.
没法反驳  我最好的朋友死了
Don't disagree. My best friend's dead.
我差点让他儿子也死了
I almost got his son killed.
反正我的刑期已经结束了
Now that my prison sentence is up,
是时候和月饼一起离开了
maybe it's a good time for me and Mooncake to move on.
- 快滚吧   - 成吧  再见了
- A great time. - All right then. Peace out.
我拿上钥匙就走
Just gonna get my keys.
我钥匙呢？
Where the crap are my keys?
哦哦哦  这是  这是几枚钢镚
Oh, oh, oh. That... That's a few coins.
哦对了  我  我没钥匙
Oh, yeah. I-I don't have keys.
好吧  呃  再次再见
Okay, well... peace out again.
奎恩 盖瑞不能走
Quinn, Gary can't leave.
随他去吧
Let him do what he wants.
你每次自己一个人做事  都以失败告终
Every time you go it alone, it ends in failure.
要想成功  你需要这个队里的每一个人
You need everyone on this crew to succeed.
直到接受这一点之前  你毫无胜算
Until you accept that, you have no chance.
但我不需要他们... 尤其不需要盖瑞
But I don't need them ... especially Gary.
他又冲动  又不负责任
He's impetuous, irresponsible,
他根本严肃不起来
and he takes nothing seriously.
哦对啊  我忘了  你还没发现吧
Oh, yeah, I forgot. You haven't figured it out yet.
我猜这是B计划了  又来一次
I guess it's plan "B." Again.
她的飞船是个时光机  我能救回我爸
Her ship's a freakin' time machine. I can save my dad.
- 你刚管我叫“爸”了吗？   - 我刚管你叫啥？
- Did you just call me dad? - Did I just call you what?
你真的要离开吗？
You're really going?
说真的  我自己都有点不信  不过我确实要走了
Surprised myself, frankly, but it is what it is.
HUE  我平时的衣服呢？
H.U.E., where are my civilian clothes?
你走了以后  我该怎么办？
What will I do when you're gone?
你是我唯一的朋友  盖瑞
You're my only friend, Gary.
真的？KVN呢？
Really? What about KVN?
KVN是个智障  盖瑞  你知道的
KVN is a jag-off, Gary. You know that.
是啊  我的确知道
Yeah, I do know that, actually.
KVN的存在就是要把所有他接触的东西都给毁了
Yeah. KVN was sent just to ruin everything he touches!
他完全就是迈达斯的反义词
He's the complete opposite of Midas.
迈达斯（Midas）：希腊神话中的弗里吉亚国王，据说他能点石成金。
KVN是... 屎达斯
Turdas ... That's KVN.
只消轻轻一碰  你人生的全部就都变成了一条细长的屎
One touch, everything in life turns into one long, slender turd.
Chocli!
什么... 你怎... 嘿！
What ... how ... hey!
你好啊  嗨  你正好赶上了
Hello. Hi. You caught me
我赤身裸体没穿裤子的时候
at a highly naked pantsless time.
Chocli. Buk, buk, buk.
喵的！
Dang it!
你知道我们在一起已经多久了吗？
Do you know how long it's been since we've been together?
- 五分钟  八分钟？   - 其实是20年
- Five, eight minutes? - More like 20 years.
- 我失去了你  我的你   - 我为你的你感到遗憾
- I lost you. My you. - That sucks for your you.
哇！喔啊！
Wah! Whoa!
我被扑在床上了  老天爷  你劲真大
I'm on the mattress. Good Lord, you are strong.
哦  真有意思  你在上面
Oh, this has been fantastic. And you're crawling on top.
不  等等  我  我的意思是
Okay, wait, you know what, I-I-I gotta say
我其实是那种更喜欢吃吃喝喝的人
I'm more of a wine and dine kind of lad.
一块饼干一杯水都能让我心满意足
Even a cracker and some water would go a long way with me,
所以... 咱能  回到正题吗...
'cause I mean ... Can we please, uh, get to the subject ...
正题就是  我已经有奎恩了
the subject matter here is that there's a Quinn thing!
我就是奎恩
I am Quinn.
我说的是我的奎恩  别想多了
I mean my Quinn. Don't get me wrong.
未来的奎恩超级性感  超级强壮
Tomorrow's Quinn is super hot and freakishly strong,
不过这份性感和强壮
but in a more tomorrow's freakishly strong
是未来的奎恩的
and hot kind of way.
好了  我得到我想要的了
All right. I got what I need.
再见了  盖瑞
Goodbye, Gary.
能量手铐？你太无礼了吧
Energy cuffs?  You are sassy.
我们戴着能量手铐说再见
We're playing goodbye with energy cuffs.
这里他妈发生了啥？！
What the hell is going on here?!
看起来你走进了一个奇妙的场合  奎恩
It seems like you walked into a situation, Quinn,
- 我俩正在...   - “我俩”？！
- where the two of us ... - "Us?!"
哦不不不不  这不是咱俩
Oh, no, no, no, no! This is not us.
不过她是你
But she's you.
- 他说得对   - 不  他说得不对！
- He's right. - No, he's not!
- 我觉得我是对的   - 我是你
- I think I am. - I am you.
不过我可不会这么做
But I'm not doing that.
这种光膀子上床的事可不是我的...
This naked bed stuff really wasn't much of a ...
- 闭嘴  盖瑞！   - 我很懵
- Shut up, Gary! - I'm confused.
我不懵  我莫名其妙地性奋起来了
I am not. I am strangely aroused.
- 我也是！   - 我都不知道我还能性奋
- Me, too! - Didn't know that could happen.
感觉怪怪的
Feels weird.
- 你滚开！   - 我反正弄完了
- Get over here! - I was done anyway.
废话少说  夜幕  我需要答案
Cut the crap, Nightfall. I want answers.
我正在试着拯救宇宙
I was trying to save the universe.
把盖瑞光膀子拷起来就能拯救宇宙了？
By handcuffing Gary naked?
我不想让他看见接下来发生的事
I don't want him to see what's happening next.
在月饼毁灭所有人之前  我要先把它杀了
I'm going to kill Mooncake before he destroys all of us.
你在说些啥啊？
What are you talking about?
你知道盖瑞身上会发生什么吗？
Do you know what's about to happen to Gary?
每次盖瑞从任务里离开
Every time Gary leaves the mission,
总司令就会把他杀死
the Lord Commander kills him.
月饼体内的某些东西折断了
Something inside Mooncake snaps.
月饼会毁灭整个宇宙
Mooncake lays waste to the universe
撕开通往终空的门
and tears open the door to Final Space.
那时  泰坦就会穿越屏障  进入我们的次元
That's when the Titans break through the barrier to our dimension.
那是最可怕的梦魇
Monstrous nightmares.
言辞不足以描绘其可怖
Words are a waste describing their horror.
住手  你不能这么做
Stop. You can't do this.
你最后会感谢我的
You'll thank me in the end.
Chocli ... agh!
月饼！
Mooncake!
Chocli, buk, buk!
月饼！
Mooncake!
Buk, buk, buk!
我要是能...
If I can just...
好的！
Yes!
夜幕要杀月饼！
Nightfall wants to kill Mooncake!
我知道！快把我救出来！
I can see that! Get me out of here!
我们必须让她住手！
We need to stop her right now!
- 太近了！   - 快穿衣服！咱们走！
-  A little close! - Get dressed! Let's go!
这最后一天太垃圾了！
This last day sucks!
Chocli! Chocli!
不要！
No!
Chocli!
Chocli! Chocli!
Chocli, choc, choc, choc!
Choc, choc, choc!
你为什么要杀月饼！
Why would you want to kill Mooncake?
- 我没有！   - 哦！
- I don't! - Ow!
她才要杀
She does.
我真为你自豪  儿子
I'm proud of you, son.
我为什么在哭？
Why am I crying?
哦  你长得这么快
Oh, you're growing up so fast.
对不起  我在这说个不停
I'm sorry, I'm just going on and on.
别闹了  你不是我爸
Stop it. You're not my dad.
因为我比你爸更棒  对不对？
'Cause I'm better than your dad, right?
没关系  你可以承认的  你可以说“是！爸我永远爱你！”
It's okay. You can admit it, you can say yes.
- 快说吧   - 不要！
- Go ahead. - No!
- 我能当你爷爷吗？   - 不
- Can I be your granddad? - No.
- 外公？  - 不
- Grandpa? - No.
- 叔叔？  - 不
- Uncle? - No.
- 表哥？  - 不
- Cousin? - No.
- 侄子？  - 不
- Nephew? - No.
- 哥哥？  - 不
- Brother? - No.
- 我能当你太爷爷吗？  - 不
- Can I be your great-granddad? - No.
- 你阿姨？  - 不
- Can I be your aunt? - No.
- 你侄女？  - 不
- Can I be your niece? - No.
- 你... 妈？  - 不不不
- Can I be your... mom? - No, no.
哇啊  看这些宇宙大冰块！
Whoa, look at all these cosmic ice cubes!
哇啊  哇啊  哇啊！
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
哦！哇啊  哇啊！
Oh!  Whoa, whoa!
哦！哇啊  酷！
Oh! Whoa, cool!
月饼！
Mooncake!
Chocli, buk, buk!
哇啊  这就不酷了！
Whoa, not cool!
你要想抓他  先得过我这一关
You've gotta go through me to get to him.
你不想这样的  相信我
You don't want to do this. Trust me.
相信盖瑞
Trust Gary.
INSIDE THE EPISODE AFTER CREDITS
奎恩  你和盖瑞说吧
Quinn, tell Gary what happens.
告诉他  我们为什么要杀月饼
Tell him why we need to kill Mooncake.
嗯  呃  好吧
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, okay.
我大约是嗑多了
Really lost in the weeds over here.
谁能给我弄明白吗？
Anybody mind whacking some clarity for me?
快告诉他！
Tell him!
- 我能当你的双胞胎吗？   - 不
- Can I be your twin? - No.
- 我能当你的任何东西吗？   - 不不不
- Can I be your anything? - No, no, no.
- 我能当你的一切吗？   - 不
- Can I be your everything? - No.
- 我能当你吗？   - 不
- Can I be you? - No.
可我想当你  我想当你！
I want to be you. I want to be you!
即将启动自毁模式
Self-destruct imminent.
时间聚合舱体泄漏
Time fusion chamber leaking.
不不不不不！等等  发生了什么？
No, no, no, no, no! Wait, what is happening?
- 我们被困住了   - 呃！悲剧了
- We're trapped. - Ugh! This is gonna end bad.
到底会怎么样  奎恩？
What is going on, Quinn?
如果你离开  总司令就会杀了你
If you leave, the Lord Commander kills you,
然后月饼就会对所有东西展开复仇
and Mooncake takes revenge on everything.
真的是所有东西
And I mean everything.
我已经在时空中回溯上百次了
I've been back hundreds of times,
唯一可行的方法只有杀掉月饼
and the only option left is to kill Mooncake.
小家伙？
Little buddy?
紧急情况
Emergency.
小卡多被困在夜幕的飞船里了
Little Cato is trapped inside Nightfall's ship.
他启动了自毁模式！进程无法终止！
He triggered the self-destruct! It can't be turned off!
小卡多  求求你了  就算为了我
Little Cato. Please. For me.
我不能让他死
I can't let him die.
月饼  我们走！
Mooncake, let's go!
Chocli-bop!
救命！
Help!
♪ 变化之风劲吹 ♪
♪ The winds of change keep blowing ♪
♪ 我们都将死去 ♪
♪ We're all gonna die ♪
♪ 变化之风... ♪
♪ Winds of change keep... ♪
♪ 不要让我走 ♪
♪ Don't let me go ♪
♪ 永远不要让我走 ♪
♪ Never let me go ♪
我们得把他们救出来  时间正在泄漏
We've gotta get them out. Time is leaking.
再过一会  他们就要消失了
In another moment, they'll be blinked out of existence.
♪ No, never let me go ♪
♪ 不  永远不要让我走 ♪
小卡多！
Little Cato!
抓住我的手！
Grab my hand!
都是我的错
It was all my fault.
- 他是因为我才死的   - 我说抓住我的手！
- He died because of me. - I said grab it!
我是如此孤独
I feel so alone.
你不孤独  我们会一起扛过去的
You're not alone. We'll get through it together.
我们是一个小组  一个小队啊
As a team. As a squad.
- 一个小团队   - 怎么可能？你不是要走了吗
- As a team squad. - How? You're leaving.
实话实说  我哪也不去
To be honest, I was never going anywhere.
我  我无处可去
I mean, I ... I got nowhere to go.
太他妈棒了  伙计
Hell yeah, dawg.
再给月饼一次机会  我能做到的
Give Mooncake one more chance. I can fix this.
盖瑞  我  我很高兴你和我们一起
Gary, I'm... glad you're sticking around.
为什么？
Why?
- 因为我需要你   - 需要我做什么？
- Because I need you. - To do what?
- 我就需要你好吗？闭嘴吧！   - 成吧
- I just need you, okay? So shut up! - Works for me.
- 那我呢？   - 我也需要你
- What about me? - You, too.
Chocli-pop?
我尤其需要你
And especially you.
什么鬼  奎恩？你根本没提到我
What the hell, Quinn? You failed to mention me.
- 好  我也需要你   - 你好呀  你需要KVN吗？
- Yes, you. - Hi, what about KVN?
你需要KVN吗？嗯？
Do you need KVN? Huh?
- 嗯？   - 是  KVN！
- Huh? - Yes, KVN!
“是”  是什么意思？
Yes, KVN, what?
我也需要你  成了吧？我需要你们所有人
I need you, too, all right? I need all of you.
那你正好加入了“把烂脾气的...
Then you just joined the Legion of Murdering...
啥啥啥...”  我也忘了  名字起太长了
something or another. I don't know. It's really long.
- 是的  你已经加入我们了   - 我希望你们闹够了
- Yeah, you did. -  I hope that's enough.
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com
幕后专访
INSIDE THE EPISODE
盖瑞那种忠诚特质  让他又帅又引人喜爱
With Gary the whole loyalty factor is what makes him so endearing and cool.
他会一直陪你到最后
He will stick with you to the very end.
我相信所有人都想要这样一个朋友
I think everybody wants a friend like that.
我们想了很久要怎么让夜幕穿越回来
We thought a lot about how Nightfall comes back.
夜幕很酷  所以我们把她留下来了
Nightfall is cool, so we went with it.
至于片中的泰坦...
The Titans of the show...
未来的几集里你们还会多次见到他们
you'll gonna have to see a lot more these Titans in future episodes,
说不定下集就能见到
and perhaps even in the next episode.